You know, there's diplomacy, and then there's negotiating with T-Wrists.
Watch the video.
I wanted to share some recent events with you guys regarding two of the communities that some of our elected officials have been meeting with this week.
We have here New York City Council Member Chiyose, Public Advocate Jemaine Williams, and New York State Assembly Member and Mayor-Elect Zohra Mamdani at an all-male meeting with the Satmar community.
The Satmar community has been in the news regarding this man, Nechemia Weberman, a convicted pedophile.
He is currently serving a 50-year prison sentence upstate, and his community is lobbying so hard to get him out of prison.
They've even gotten the Brooklyn District Attorney, Eric Gonzalez, to take up the cause for them.
And recently, two rabbis from their community signed on to a letter, along with many other rabbis, asking Governor Kathy Hochul to commute this man's sentence.
He is a convicted pedophile.
Zohran, pictured here meeting with the Chabad Lubavitch, this is the group that earlier this year, some of their members assaulted a black man in a wheelchair.
How can you do that to a man in a wheelchair?
And also at a rally this year in April, denouncing radical Jewish supremacist war criminal Ben Gavir's presence.
Chabad members came out and violently attacked the mostly female group of protesters, throwing me to the ground, hitting one woman in the head with possibly a brick.
And then in the most heinous event that night, they chased a lone woman, hundreds of them, chased a lone woman, assaulted her multiple times, threw safety cones and trash cans at her, as well as threw rape threats at her.
I don't want someone to bend you over and fucking rape you like they're doing Jews in fucking Palestine.
None of the perpetrators have been arrested, by the way.
They are very closely tied to the colonization of Palestine.
They have their signs and their flags all over occupied Palestine.
And here is a video of their Grand Rabbi, who Zohran Mamdani was just praying on his grave site, telling Benjamin Milikowski, i.e. Netanyahu, to work faster.
I want one сюда, but you want to explain all my ashes, but there is nothing to add to that.
And this is something that I would imagine here.
And this is everything I want to say for everyone in the world.
To fight for the years, through sharing everything he wants, the needs and the needs that ETF lives.
Keeping your beliefs on the bond that he loves and who still keeps calling him back and you know what he looks for to come,
Three things that he wants is what spirit from him and what is happening.
Take control, take control.
The critique that he makes a proper type of truth will transform his mind.
Habad Lubavitch is also the group well-known
for their tunnels.
Best case scenario here is that these three
are trying to infiltrate to disintegrate.
Otherwise, WTF.
I don't know if it's just that they don't care
if they think that they can interact with these people
and thus will get them to bend and shift to their will
on certain things.
I don't know if maybe they're understaffed
and thus didn't have the capability to do the research
that this lovely woman, Jen, has done.
But Jumaine, this is ridiculous as a Grenadian.
She, weren't you the other one the other day
talking about you're livid about Momdani
and now you hanging out with him in the worst of places?
And Momdani, well, you know, I don't know.
Take it up with your dad.
Support a real one.